<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Chem 2440 Ising Model</title>
    <link>https://amandadumi.github.io/statmech_python_tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Chem 2440 Ising Model</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 16:02:06 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amandadumi.github.io/statmech_python_tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Session03</title>
      <link>https://amandadumi.github.io/statmech_python_tutorials/session03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 16:15:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandadumi.github.io/statmech_python_tutorials/session03/</guid>
      <description>Mathematical notation and writing to files Obtaining Materials For our last session, we will be downloading materials from online. Click here to download the directory as a .zip file. Unzip the repository. Navigate to statmech_python_tutorials/materials/session03_math_io/. Here you will find the jupyter notebook we will work from session03_math_io.ipynb. Launch Jupyter Notebook and work through the exercises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session02</title>
      <link>https://amandadumi.github.io/statmech_python_tutorials/session02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 16:15:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandadumi.github.io/statmech_python_tutorials/session02/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started Python is a computer programming language that has become ubiquitous in scientific programming. Our initial lessons will run python interactively through a python interpreter. We will first use a Jupyter notebook. The [setup] page should have provided information on how to install and start a Jupyter notebook. Everything included in a code block is something you could type into your python interpreter and evaluate.
Setting up your Jupyter notebooks In the [setup], you learned how to start a Jupyter notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Session 01 - Install Python and Jupyter</title>
      <link>https://amandadumi.github.io/statmech_python_tutorials/session01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 16:15:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandadumi.github.io/statmech_python_tutorials/session01/</guid>
      <description>Session 01 - Install Python and Jupyter Installing Python through Anaconda Python is a popular language for scientific computing, and great for general-purpose programming as well. Installing all of its scientific packages individually can be a bit difficult, however, so we recommend the all-in-one installer Anaconda.
 Navigate to the download page for Anaconda. Download the appropriate installer for your operating system. Make sure you get the installer listed under Python 3 (not 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://amandadumi.github.io/statmech_python_tutorials/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amandadumi.github.io/statmech_python_tutorials/about/</guid>
      <description>Python Introduction for CHEM 2440 Statistical Mechanics</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
